const AI_quiz3 = [
    {
        "question": "A search algorithm is said to be complete when gives a solution or returns any solution for a random input.",
        "options": [
            "Completeness",
            "Optimality",
            "Time complexity",
            "Space complexity" 
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Completeness"
    },
    {
        "question": "If a solution found is best (lowest path cost) among the solutions identified, then that solution is said be an optimal one.",
        "options": [
            "Completeness",
            "Optimality",
            "Time complexity",
            "Space complexity" 
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Optimality"
    },
    {
        "question": "The time taken by an algorithm to complete its task called time complexity. If the algorithm completes task in a lesser amount of time, then it is an one.",
        "options": [
            "Completeness",
            "Optimality",
            "Time complexity",
            "Space complexity" 
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Time complexity"
    },
	{
	    "question": "It is of the most common search strategies. It generally starts from the root node and examines the neighbor nodes and then moves to the next level. It uses First-in First-out (FIFO) strategy as it gives the shortest path to achieving the solution",
	    "options": [
	        "Breadth-first search",
	        "Depth-first search",
	        "Depth-limited search",
	        "Iterative deepening depth-first search"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "Breadth-first search"
	},
	{
	    "question": "The ______ uses Last-in, First-(LIFO) strategy and hence it can be implemented by using stack. ",
	    "options": [
	        "Breadth-first search",
	        "Depth-first search",
	        "Depth-limited search",
	        "Iterative deepening depth-first search"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "Depth-first search"
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which search algorithm limits the depth of exploration to a certain level before backtracking?",
	    "options": [
	        "Breadth-first search",
	        "Depth-first search",
	        "Depth-limited search",
	        "Iterative deepening depth-first search"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "Depth-limited search"
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which search algorithm combines the advantages of depth-first search and breadth-first search by gradually increasing the depth limit?",
	    "options": [
	        "Breadth-first search",
	        "Depth-first search",
	        "Depth-limited search",
	        "Iterative deepening depth-first search"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "Iterative deepening depth-first search"
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which search algorithm explores from both the start and goal (or end) nodes simultaneously and stops when the two meet in the middle?",
	    "options": [
	        "Bidirectional search",
	        "Depth-first search",
	        "Breadth-first search",
	        "Uniform cost search"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "Bidirectional search"
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which search algorithm guarantees that it finds the shortest path from the start node to the goal node based on the cost of each step?",
	    "options": [
	        "Bidirectional search",
	        "Uniform cost search",
	        "Depth-limited search",
	        "Depth-first search"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "Uniform cost search"
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which search algorithm chooses the node that appears to be closest to the goal based on a heuristic function?",
	    "options": [
	        "Greedy best-first search algorithm",
	        "Fuzzy search  algorithm",
	        "Sequential search algorithm",
	        "A* search algorithm"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "Greedy best-first search algorithm"
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which search algorithm chooses the node that appears to be the best combination of cost and heuristic value based on a heuristic function?",
	    "options": [
	        "Greedy best-first search algorithm",
	        "Fuzzy search  algorithm",
	        "Sequential search algorithm",
	        "A* search algorithm"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "A* search algorithm"
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which search strategy has no additional information about the state space beyond that provided in the problem definition?",
	    "options": [
	        "Uninformed search",
	        "Informed search",
	        "Heuristic search",
	        "Optimal search"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "Uninformed search"
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which search strategy uses additional information about the state space to guide the search?",
	    "options": [
	        "Uninformed search",
	        "Informed search",
	        "Heuristic search",
	        "Optimal search"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "Informed search"
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is an advantage of using breadth-first search?",
	    "options": [
	        "It will never be trapped in any unwanted nodes",
	        "It always expands the least number of nodes",
	        "It is less memory intensive than depth-first search",
	        "It always finds the optimal solution"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "BFS will never be trapped in any unwanted nodes"
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is an advantage of using depth-first search?",
	    "options": [
	        "It requires less memory than breadth-first search",
	        "It is guaranteed to find the shortest path to the goal state",
	        "It always expands the least number of nodes",
	        "It is more informed than other search algorithms"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "It requires less memory than breadth-first search"
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is an advantage of using depth-limited search?",
	    "options": [
	        "It takes lesser memory when compared to other search techniques",
	        "It always guarantees finding the optimal solution",
	        "It is less memory intensive than other search algorithms",
	        "It provides more information about the state space than other search algorithms"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "It takes lesser memory when compared to other search techniques"
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is an advantage of using bidirectional search?",
	    "options": [
	        "It searches the graph fast",
	        "It always finds the optimal solution",
	        "It requires less memory than other search algorithms",
	        "It provides more information about the state space than other search algorithms"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "It searches the graph fast"
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is an advantage of using uniform cost search?",
	    "options": [
	        "It  is optimal as the selection of paths is based on the lowest cost",
	        "It requires less memory than other search algorithms",
	        "It is less time consuming than other search algorithms",
	        "It can handle any type of state space without modification"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "It  is optimal as the selection of paths is based on the lowest cost"
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is an advantage of using iterative deepening depth-first search?",
	    "options": [
	        "It guarantees finding the optimal solution",
	        "It requires less memory than other search algorithms",
	        "It can handle any type of state space without modification",
	        "It combines the advantages of both depth-first search and breadth-first search"
	    ],
	    "correctAnswer": "It combines the advantages of both depth-first search and breadth-first search"
	}
]
